A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller, Vice Presidential records xFA250
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Speeches, 1974-1977; 15; 23 Cubic Feet 23 Boxes 23 cubic feet
  - Wilkins, Roy (Box 10, Folder 377)
  - Williamsburg (Box 10, Folder 378)
  - Women (Box 10, Folder 379)
  - World Bank (Box 10, Folder 380)
  - World Trade Center (Box 10, Folder 381)
  - Youth (Box 10, Folder 382)
  - September 23-25, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 383)
    Washington, DC; Beginning of Hearings before Senate Committee on Rules and Administration; 72 page document issued on history of family, family business, NAR chronology.
  - September 23-25, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 384)
  - October 2, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 385)
    Provo, Utah, Brigham Young University; Message from President Ford; praise for Brigham Young University, confirmation hearings.
  - October 2, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 386)
    San Francisco, CA; 15th Annual Conference of Editors and Publishers; message from President Ford, freedom of information, confirmation hearings.
  - October 7, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 387)
    New York, Cooper Union; Great Hall Forum Program; Commission on Critical Choices for Americans.
  - October 8, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 388)
    Warrenton, VA; 6th Annual Statement In Medicine Award Dinner; award to Dr. C. Rollins Hanlon.
  - October 16, 1974 (canceled) (Box 10, Folder 389)
    Foreign Policy Association Luncheon.
  - October 25, 1974 (canceled) (Box 10, Folder 390)
    North Tarrytown, NY, Dedication, Phelps Memorial Hospital.
  - November 13, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 391)
    Washington, DC; Re-opening of Hearings, Senate Rules Committee.
  - November 13, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 392)
    Washington, DC; Committee on Rules and Administration.
  - November 21, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 393)
    Washington, DC; Opening of House Judiciary Committee Confirmation Hearing.
  - November 24, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 394)
    House Judiciary Committee Statement.
  - December 3, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 395)
    Washington, DC; Luncheon with Freshman Republican Congressmen.
  - December 5, 1974 (Empty folder) (Box 10, Folder 396)
    Washington, DC; Second Appearance, House Judiciary Committee.
  - December 19, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 397)
    Washington, DC; Swearing-In as Vice President in Senate Chamber.
  - January 10, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 398)
    Washington, DC; Toast and Luncheon for the Sultan of Oman; toasts.
  - January 13, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 399)
    Washington, DC; Briefing, Central Intelligence Agency; CIA Activities in the United States.
  - January 16, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 400)
    Washington, DC; Briefing, Presidential Appointees; Ford.
  - January 16, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 401)
    Washington, DC; Briefing, Governors & Mayors; local government.
  - January 21, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 402)
    Washington, DC; American Trucking Association, Outstanding Driver of the Year; traffic safety.
  - January 22, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 403)
    Washington, DC; GOP Congressional Campaign Committee Reception; Ford, honor to work with Ford.
  - January 23, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 404)
    Washington, DC; Swearing-In Ceremony, Nuclear Regulatory Commissioners; nuclear energy.
  - January 23, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 405)
    Chicago, IL; National Business Leadership conference sponsored by Junior Achievement; economy, administration's programs.
  - January 24, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 406)
    Washington, DC; Swearing-In of Marjorie Lynch, Deputy Administrator of the Bicentennial Administration; Bicentennial.
  - January 24, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 407)
    Washington, DC; Bicentennial.
  - January 28, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 408)
    Washington, DC; Washington Press Club Interview; miscellaneous humorous questions and answers.
  - January 28, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 409)
    Washington, DC; World Wildlife Fund, Getty Prize for Conservation; conservation, environment.
  - January 29, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 410)
    Milburn, NJ; GOP Fund Raising Dinner; energy & economy.
  - January 31, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 411)
    Washington, DC; Swearing-In, President's Panel on Biomedical Research; health.
  - January 31, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 412)
    Washington, DC; Dinner given by Prime Minister and Mrs. Wilson; foreign affairs, relationship of United States and Britain.
  - February 4, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 413)
    Washington, DC; United States Travel Service Conference; tourism.
  - February 5, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 414)
    Washington, DC; Meeting with Pine Crest Students; history.
  - February 6, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 415)
    Washington, DC; Prime Minister Bhutto dinner; toast.
  - February 13, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 416)
    New York, Waldorf Astoria; Dinner, Honoring Vice President; Ford, admiration of Ford's leadership.
  - February 14, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 417)
    New York, Waldorf Astoria; Governors Club Dinner; governors.
  - February 19, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 418)
    Washington, DC; National Governor's Conference; local government, government programs.
  - February 19, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 419)
    Washington, DC; United States Chamber of Commerce, Breakfast; energy.
  - February 19, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 420)
    Washington, DC; Pan American Union, Reception for Felipe Benavides; testimonial.
  - February 21, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 421)
    Washington, DC; Republican Governors' Breakfast; republican Party and Domestic Council.
  - February 21, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 422)
    Washington, DC; Grocery Manufacturers of America; miscellaneous.
  - February 21, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 423)
    Washington, DC; Black Enterprise Achievement Awards; African-Americans.
  - February 25, 1975 (canceled) (Box 11, Folder 424)
    Washington, DC; National Bicentennial Commission.
  - February 26, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 425)
    Washington, DC; SOS and Chowder and Marching Society Breakfast; Domestic Council, energy, economy.
  - February 26, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 426)
    Detroit, MI; Society of Automotive Engineers; energy.
  - February 26, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 427)
    Washington, DC; South Carolina Young Republicans; Republican Party.
  - February 27, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 428)
    Arthur S. Flemming Awards; government and private sector.
  - March 4, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 429)
    Washington, DC; Meeting with Consumers Leaders; consumers.
  - March 4, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 430)
    Washington, DC; National Conference of Christians and Jews, Brotherhood Award presented to George Meany; miscellaneous.
  - March 7, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 431)
    Washington, DC; Republican Leadership Conference; Republican Party.
  - March 21, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 432)
    Washington, DC; Meeting with Coal Industry; energy.
  - March 22, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 433)
    Washington, DC; Meeting and Gridiron Dinner; political humor, politics.
  - March 25, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 434)
    Washington, DC; Meeting with Agency Directors of Equal Employment; employment.
  - March 25, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 435)
    Washington, DC; Alfred Sloan Fellows Meeting; commerce and industry, management of industry.
  - April 3, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 436)
    Washington, DC; Outstanding Handicapped Federal Employees Awards; health, employment.
  - NOT USED (Box 11, Folder 437)
  - April 7, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 438)
    Washington, DC; Swearing-In Ceremony, Henry P. Smith III; miscellaneous.
  - April 8, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 439)
    Washington, DC; Young American Awards Presentation, outstanding youth presented by Boy Scouts; youth.
  - April 9, 1975 (canceled) (Box 11, Folder 440)
    Washington, DC; United States Government Savings Bonds Kick-Off Meeting.
  - April 9, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 441)
    Washington, DC; American Newspaper Publisher's Association; federal spending, energy, environment.
  - April 10, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 442)
    Washington, DC; President's Commission on Personnel Interchange; economy, free enterprise.
  - April 10, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 443)
    Washington, DC; Meeting with White House Fellows; Vice President's responsibilities.
  - April 11, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 444)
    Washington, DC; National Association of Manufacturers; productivity.
  - April 13, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 445)
    Chiang-Kai-Shek Funeral Statement.
  - April 15, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 446)
    Washington, DC; Reception, Senate-House Dinner; introduction of Ford and his policies.
  - April 15, 1975 (canceled) (Box 11, Folder 447)
    Washington, DC; National Commission on International Women's Year.
  - April 15, 1975 (canceled) (Box 11, Folder 448)
    Washington, DC; Republican Senate/House Dinner.
  - April 18, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 449)
    Boca Raton, FL; The Young President's Organization; productivity, economy, free enterprise.
  - April 23, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 450)
    Washington, DC; The Advertizing Council, Inc.; free enterprise.
  - April 23, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 451)
    Washington, DC; Presentation of Shakespeare Books.
  - April 23, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 452)
    Washington, DC; Reception and Banquet, National Academy of Engineering, Presentation of first Marconi International Fellowship; science and technology.
  - April 24, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 453)
    Washington, DC; American Revolution Bicentennial Exhibit; 175th Anniversary for the Library of Congress.
  - April 24, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 454)
    Washington, DC; National Volunteer Awards; government.
  - April 24, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 455)
    New York; New York Senate Campaign Committee Fund-Raiser; Republican Party.
  - April 29, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 456)
    Washington, DC; Garden Clubs of America; environment.
  - April 29, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 457)
    Washington, DC; International Session of the United States Chamber of Commerce; government, regulation.
  - April 30, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 458)
    Washington, DC; King Hussein Dinner; toast.
  - May 1, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 459)
    Washington, DC; National Urban Coalition Steering Committee; Domestic Council, revenue sharing.
  - May 6, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 460)
    Washington, DC; Institutional Investors Institute; free enterprise.
  - May 6, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 461)
    Washington, DC; Capitol Hill Club Reception Honoring Vice President; Ford.
  - May 7, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 462)
    Washington, DC; Toast to Australian Prime Minister; toasts.
  - May 7, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 463)
    Washington, DC; Archives of American Art; art.
  - May 9, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 464)
    Hot Springs, VA, The Homestead; Business Council; free enterprise, energy, economy.
  - May 12, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 465)
    Washington, DC; Federal City Council Board of Trustees Luncheon; cities.
  - May 13, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 466)
    New York, Museum of Modern Art; Reception; art.
  - May 14, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 467)
    Washington, DC; Long Island Businessmen Meeting; productivity.
  - May 15, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 468)
    Washington, DC; National Press Club, Bill Miller; testimonial.
  - May 16, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 469)
    Washington, DC; Republican Heritage Groups; ethnics.
  - May 17, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 470)
    Washington, DC; Dinner, Shah of Iran; toast.
  - May 18, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 471)
    Pocantico Hills, NY; Dinner, Shah of Iran; toasts.
  - May 19, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 472)
    National Conference on Capital Investment and Employment.
    (no speech in file)
  - May 20, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 473)
    Washington, DC; Meeting, Congressional Black Caucus; African Americans.
  - May 21, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 474)
    Washington, DC; Bull Elephant's Luncheon; government.
  - May 21, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 475)
    Washington, DC; Recording for the Blind Awards; handicapped, health.
  - May 21, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 476)
    Washington, DC; Galo Plaza Dinner; testimonial.
  - May 28, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 477)
    Washington, DC; Swearing-In of Ambassador William Lane; miscellaneous.
  - May 28, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 478)
    Washington, DC; Task Group Meeting; drugs.
  - May 29, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 479)
    Washington, DC; White House Fellows Reunion; miscellaneous.
  - May 30, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 480)
    Washington, DC; United States-Romanian Economic Council; foreign relations.
  - June 4, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 481)
    Annapolis, MD; United States Naval Academy commencement Exercises; defense.
  - June 4, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 482)
  - June 4, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 483)
    Washington, DC; New York Stock Exchange.
  - June 6, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 484)
    Washington, DC; Sigma Delta Chi, National Press Club; media.
  - June 6, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 485)
    Washington, DC; Testimony before Senator Kennedy's Joint Science Committee; science.
  - June 10, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 486)
    Washington, DC; Testimony before Congressman Teague's Science and Technology Committee; science.
  - June 12, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 487)
    New York; New York State Republican Committee Luncheon.
  - June 12, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 488)
    New York; New York State Republican Committee Dinner; Republican Party.
  - June 23, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 489)
    Washington, DC; Work Productivity Meeting; productivity.
  - June 24, 1975 (Empty folder) (Box 12, Folder 490)
    Washington, DC; National Productivity Conference; productivity.
  - July 9, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 491)
    Atlanta, GA; Public Meeting, National Commission on Water Quality; environment.
  - July 10, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 492)
    Washington, DC; Meeting of Mayors; revenue sharing.
  - July 16, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 493)
    Washington, DC; Meeting with Science Youth Group; science.
  - July 22, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 494)
    Cincinnati, OH; Midwest Governors' Conference; energy.
  - August 5, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 495)
    Washington, DC; White House Summer Interns; miscellaneous, Vice President's duties.
  - August 5, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 496)
    Washington, DC; Congress of the Deaf; health.
  - August 6, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 497)
    Washington, DC; Health Care Productivity Center; productivity, health.
  - August 6, 1975 (canceled) (Box 12, Folder 498)
    Washington, DC; Compensation Panel Hearings.
  - August 22, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 499)
    Seal Harbor, ME; Maine Republican Reception; Republican Party.
  - August 26, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 500)
    Mobile, AL; Lieutenant Governors Conference; Domestic Council forums.
  - August 27, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 501)
    Columbia, SC; GOP Reception.
  - August 27, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 502)
    Columbia, SC; Gov. Edwards' Luncheon; Republican Party re the South.
  - September 5, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 503)
    Rochester, NY; Dedication of Family Medical Center at Highland Hospital; health.
  - September 5, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 504)
    Greece, NY; Dedication of Park Ridge Hospital; health.
  - September 5, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 505)
    Rochester, NY; United States Savings Bond Drive; savings bonds.
  - September 5, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 506)
    Rochester, NY; Monroe County Chairman's Club Reception; Monroe County.
  - September 10, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 507)
    Washington, DC; Capitol Hill Club Reception; Ford and his Administration.
  - September 10, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 508)
    Washington, DC; Savings Bond Award Ceremony; savings bonds.
  - September 11, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 509)
    Washington, DC; "Life Magazine" Bicentennial Issue; Bicentennial.
  - September 12, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 510)
    Little Rock, AR; Arkansas events; Winthrop Rockefeller & Republican Party.
  - September 12, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 511)
    Dallas, TX; National Federation of Republican Women Convention; women, government, Republican Party.
  - September 13, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 512)
    Enid, OK; Airport Reception.
  - September 13, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 513)
    Enid, OK; Republican Dinner; energy, domestic programs.
  - September 13, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 514)
    Norman, OK; GOP Campaign Brunch; miscellaneous information about Oklahoma.
  - September 15, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 515)
    London, England, British Museum; "The World of Franklin and Jefferson" Bicentennial Exhibit; bicentennial.
  - September 17, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 516)
    Washington, DC, National Archives; Reading Is Fundamental Ceremony; bicentennial.
  - September 18, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 517)
    Washington, DC, State Department; National Medal of Science Luncheon; science.
  - September 18, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 518)
    Washington, DC; British Embassy Dinner in honor of Member of Parliament Margaret Thatcher; NAR Toast to Mrs. Thatcher.
  - September 24, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 519)
    Washington, DC; Vice President's Office; Presentation of "Pulick Occurrences," (first newspaper); Bicentennial, journalism.
  - September 26, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 520)
    Pocantico, NY; County Chairmen's Luncheon; Republican Party (New York state).
  - September 29, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 521)
    Washington, DC, Madison Hotel; Federal City Council Meeting; government.
  - October 2, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 522)
    Washington, DC, Madison Hotel; The National Energy Project Conference; energy.
  - October 3, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 523)
    Portland, OR; Western States Republican Breakfast; miscellaneous.
  - October 3, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 524)
    Portland, OR; Republican Reception; miscellaneous.
  - October 3, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 525)
    Portland, OR; Western States Republican Conference; Republican Party.
  - October 6, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 526)
    Washington, DC, Vice President's Office; Energy Independence Authority Briefing; energy.
  - October 7, 1975 (canceled) (Box 13, Folder 527)
    Washington, DC, Shoreham Hotel; "Change" Magazine Luncheon.
  - October 7, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 528)
    Kings Mountain, NC; Kings Mountain Bicentennial Celebration; bicentennial.
  - October 8, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 529)
    Washington, DC, Vice President's Office; Roundtable on Privacy and Information; privacy.
  - October 10, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 530)
    Washington, DC; Toast to King Olav; toast.
  - October 11, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 531)
    Newport News, VA; Eisenhower Ship Launching; defense, navy.
  - October 11, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 532)
    New York, Waldorf Astoria; Columbus Day Dinner; New York City.
  - October 15, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 533)
    Columbus, OH; Republican Leadership Meeting; Republican Party.
  - October 15, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 534)
    Columbus, OH; Republican State Committee Dinner; inflation, defense, government.
  - October 16, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 535)
    Charleston, WV; Executive Club Luncheon; energy.
  - October 16, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 536)
    Charleston, WV; West Virginia Reception; Ford and his policies.
  - October 16, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 537)
    Roanoke, VA; GOP Fund-Raising Reception; Republican Party.
  - October 21, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 538)
    Denver, CO; Public Forum on Domestic Policy; Domestic Council.
  - October 22, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 539)
    Washington, DC; Republican Congressional Wives Luncheon; miscellaneous re Congressional wives.
  - October 22, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 540)
    Washington, DC, Vice President's Office; Congressman Brown Visit; talking points on energy.
  - October 23, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 541)
    Indianapolis, IN; GOP Luncheon; economy.
  - October 23, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 542)
    Indianapolis, IN; Indiana State Teachers Association; education.
  - October 23, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 543)
    Indianapolis, IN; GOP Reception; miscellaneous.
  - October 23, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 544)
    Decatur, IL; Macon County Republican Dinner; politics, domestic problems.
  - October 24, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 545)
    Milwaukee, WI; Business-Labor Luncheon; government, domestic problems.
  - October 24, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 546)
    Milwaukee, WI; Founders Club Reception; Republican Party.
  - October 24, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 547)
    Milwaukee, WI; United Negro College Fund Dinner; African-Americans, education.
  - October 29, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 548)
    Tampa, FL; Domestic Public Forum; Domestic Council.
  - October 30, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 549)
    Pocantico, NY; Lunch with President Sadat; toast.
  - October 30, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 550)
    New York; Hebrew Union College; religion.
  - October 31, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 551)
    Houston, TX; Dinner for President Sadat; toast.
  - November 5, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 552)
    Washington, DC, Capitol Hill; Foreign Relations Committee Luncheon for President Sadat; toast.
  - November 10, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 553)
    Washington, DC, Vice President's Office; Presentation of Labor Department Design Manual; miscellaneous.
  - November 10, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 554)
    Austin, TX; Conference of Women in Public Life; women.
  - November 11, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 555)
    Austin, TX; Public Forum on Domestic Policy; Domestic Council.
  - November 14, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 556)
    Kansas City, MO; Future Farmers of America; agriculture.
  - November 14, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 557)
    Lincolnshire, IL; McClory Testimonial Dinner.
  - November 15, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 558)
    St. Cloud, MN; Minnesota Republican State Convention; Republican Party.
  - November 15, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 559)
    St. Paul, MN; Elephant Club Reception; government, Republican Party.
  - November 15, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 560)
    St. Cloud, MN; Metropolitan State College; energy.
  - November 15, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 561)
    St. Paul, MN; GOP Fund Raiser Dinner; Republican Party.
  - NOT USED (Box 14, Folder 562)
  - November 18, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 563)
    Philadelphia, PA; Public Forum on Domestic Policy; Domestic Council.
  - November 19, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 564)
    Washington, DC; Council of 100 Dinner; African Americans.
  - November 21, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 565)
    Wichita, KS; Republican Governors Conference; energy.
  - November 21, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 566)
    Wichita, KS; Breakfast with Governors; Vice Presidential withdrawal, miscellaneous.
  - November 21, 1975 (canceled) (Box 14, Folder 567)
    Wichita, KS; Luncheon with Kansas GOP Leaders.
  - November 25, 1975 (canceled) (Box 14, Folder 568)
    New York; United Jewish Appeal Dinner; Jews, Middle East.
  - November 25, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 569)
    Indianapolis, IN; Public Forum on Domestic Policy; Domestic Council.
  - December 2, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 570)
    New York; New York State GOP Reception; local government.
  - December 3, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 571)
    New York; NAR testimony before Urban Development Corporation Hearings (Moreland Act Commission); Urban Development Corporation (UDC), housing, revenue financing.
  - December 3, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 572)
  - December 4, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 573)
    Pittsburg, PA; Republican National Committee, Private Reception; Republican Party.
  - December 4, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 574)
    Washington, DC, Vice President's Office; Presentation of Federal Women Awards; women.
  - December 4, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 575)
    Pittsburgh, PA; Republican Awards Dinner, Tribute to Hugh Scott; testimonial.
  - December 5, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 576)
    New York; National Association of Manufacturers; energy.
  - December 9, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 577)
    Los Angeles, CA; Public Forum on Domestic Policy; Domestic Council.
  - December 10, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 578)
    Washington, DC; Council on Environmental Quality Luncheon; environment.
  - December 10, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 579)
    Washington, DC; Booster Club Reception, Army-Navy Club; Republican Party, need to support incumbent Republican candidates.
  - December 11, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 580)
    Nashville, TN; Republican State Committee Fund-Raising Luncheon; energy.
  - December 11, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 581)
    Nashville, TN; Reception for Tennessee Contributors, Home of Pat Wilson; Republican Party.
  - December 11, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 582)
    Houston, TX; GOP Cocktail Reception; Republican Party.
  - December 11, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 583)
    Houston, TX; State GOP Reception (Black GOP Leaders); Blacks and Republican Party.
  - December 11, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 584)
    Houston, TX; Houston Business & Professional Men's Club Dinner; economy.
  - December 12, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 585)
    Houston, TX; Republican National Committee Reception; Republican Party.